<resources xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<string key="9202_00_Hunter_Dialogue" comment="n/a" speaker="Ajax Halfhand - Weaver's Fen" name="AjaxHalfhand" gender="Male" VO_Status="Needs Recording" rel_version="Quest_MSQ2_WeaversFen">Nevermind the skeletons or the unded. This land belongs to nature. As do all lands. It is our lot to respect , not dominate it.\n\nI heartily recommend you take precautions. Stock up on food, drink, and merriment of spirit.</string>
	<string key="9202_01_Hunter_Dialogue" comment="bow intro" speaker="Ajax Halfhand - Weaver's Fen" name="AjaxHalfhand" gender="Male" VO_Status="Needs Recording" rel_version="Quest_MSQ2_WeaversFen">Long ago, there was a Huntress in the Fen with the most amazing bow you have ever seen. I think I know how to fashion one just like it.\n\nIt will require tracking and hunting beasts of great power, if you're up for the challenge.</string>
	<string key="9202_02_Hunter_Dialogue" comment="post - bow" speaker="Ajax Halfhand - Weaver's Fen" name="AjaxHalfhand" gender="Male" VO_Status="Needs Recording" rel_version="Quest_MSQ2_WeaversFen">People are already talking about that bow - the Huntress. She's beautiful, I tell you.\n\nJust don't tell anyone where you got the tip. Can't give that information to just anyone!</string>
	<string key="9208_00_Shaman_Dialogue" comment="n/a" speaker="Fiona Harrower - Weaver's Fen" name="FionaHarrower" gender="Female" VO_Status="Needs Recording" rel_version="Quest_MSQ2_WeaversFen">What do you see? Your eyes unaided and soft. So innocent yet.\n\nI see hunger in you. Like that of an owl. A pasison ready to fly. But you have no wings.</string>
	<string key="9208_01_Shaman_Dialogue" comment="post wyrd" speaker="Fiona Harrower - Weaver's Fen" name="FionaHarrower" gender="Female" VO_Status="Needs Recording" rel_version="Quest_MSQ2_WeaversFen">You have talons sharp. And a beak for hunting. But I see no wings on you, little bird.\n\nI can tell you where to find them. I can teach you how to soar.</string>
	<string key="9208_02_Shaman_Dialogue" comment="post wyrd" speaker="Fiona Harrower - Weaver's Fen" name="FionaHarrower" gender="Female" VO_Status="Needs Recording" rel_version="Quest_MSQ2_WeaversFen">May your armor guard you against malicious intent on Aeternum.\n\nMay you receive as much aid as you have given to others.</string>
	<string key="9203_00_FirePriest_Dialogue" comment="n/a" speaker="Hariq Azar - Brightwood" name="HariqAzar" gender="Male" VO_Status="Needs Recording" rel_version="Quest_MSQ2_WeaversFen">In the hearth she is there, eyes blazing with wrath. I hear her in my dreams, sowing seeds of fire readying her vengeance with burning fury.\n\nOne day we will all be consumed by her cleansing flame. I hope you are there to stand and greet the blinding light.</string>
	<string key="9203_01_FirePriest_Dialogue" comment="staff intro" speaker="Hariq Azar - Brightwood" name="HariqAzar" gender="Male" VO_Status="Needs Recording" rel_version="Quest_MSQ2_WeaversFen">Hello, seeker! Have you found what you came to the island for? \n\nFire provides the answers. It whispers the way ahead with a crackle and a hiss.</string>
	<string key="9203_02_FirePriest_Dialogue" comment="post-staff" speaker="Hariq Azar - Brightwood" name="HariqAzar" gender="Male" VO_Status="Needs Recording" rel_version="Quest_MSQ2_WeaversFen">Spend time alone at a fireplace and really listen to the flames. \n\nYou never know. Falmea may whisper to you as well.</string>
	<string key="9205_00_Blademaster_Dialogue" speaker="Tillian Parsons – Weaver's Fen" name="TillianParsons" gender="Female" VO_Status="Needs Recording" rel_version="Quest_MSQ2_WeaversFen">Welcome to the Fen. There are many a strange character about these parts. Best to watch your back, and your pockets.\n\nIt isn't all bad though, there is many pure hearted a soul to defend. One thing about this island, evil may not sleep, but that means valor is always given a chance to shine.</string>
	<string key="9205_01_Blademaster_Dialogue" speaker="Tillian Parsons – Weaver's Fen" name="TillianParsons" gender="Female" VO_Status="Needs Recording" rel_version="Quest_MSQ2_WeaversFen">You know, I was thinking, my days of swashbuckling are few and far between lately.\n\nI've been sitting on an idea for a sword sharp enough to slice a stone block. That something you'd care for?</string>
	<string key="9205_02_Blademaster_Dialogue" speaker="Tillian Parsons – Weaver's Fen" name="TillianParsons" gender="Female" VO_Status="Needs Recording" rel_version="Quest_MSQ2_WeaversFen">Seeing that blade strapped to your belt brings me great pride, {playerName}.\n\nIf ever there were a fighter worthy to wield the "Keen Temper", I'm looking right at them.</string>
	<string key="9207_00_Rogue_Dialogue" speaker="Julien Blackthorn – Weaver's Fen" name="JulienBlackthorn" gender="Female" VO_Status="Needs Recording" rel_version="Quest_MSQ2_WeaversFen">Psst, hey you. Come here and listen. Stick to the shadows if you want to live. There are montrous fiends about, the best way to survive is to not be seen.</string>
	<string key="9207_01_Rogue_Dialogue" speaker="Julien Blackthorn – Weaver's Fen" name="JulienBlackthorn" gender="Female" VO_Status="Needs Recording" rel_version="Quest_MSQ2_WeaversFen">Psst, noisy one. It's more efficient to skulk about than to leave yourself open to attacks. \n\nIf you're interested, I know of a set of armor that might help you be as silent as a shadow.</string>
	<string key="9207_02_Rogue_Dialogue" speaker="Julien Blackthorn – Weaver's Fen" name="JulienBlackthorn" gender="Female" VO_Status="Needs Recording" rel_version="Quest_MSQ2_WeaversFen">Plundering that armor was a mighty feat. Now you're a true shadow, not just in looks, but in deeds.\n\nMake no mistake, there'll be tales about you someday, just you wait.</string>
	<string key="9204_Executioner_00_Dialogue" comment="n/a" speaker="Joseph Black - Brightwood" name="JosephBlack" gender="Male" VO_Status="Needs Recording" rel_version="Quest_MSQ2_WeaversFen">Do you hear them? The writhing, groaning, lecherous fiends. All clamouring for the mercy of a final blade that will not come.\n\nBut that doesn't lessen the satisfaction of a mighty swing from a whetted axe. My days of executions in the old world may be over, but Aeternum has ample opportunities for dealing death. I'd be glad to relay the ways of the deathdealer, if you are so inclined.</string>
	<string key="9204_Executioner_01_Dialogue" comment="post - insanity to executioner" speaker="Joseph Black - Brightwood" name="JosephBlack" gender="Male" VO_Status="Needs Recording" rel_version="Quest_MSQ2_WeaversFen">I've been a headsman for decades. The wife told me I ought to seek a salvation, so I'm here. Don't feel any different... \n\nThis island could be a paradise for folks like you and me. We get to kill the same poor soul a thousand times. Let me teach you to forge your own blade of sin.</string>
	<string key="9204_Executioner_02_Dialogue" comment="post executioner" speaker="Joseph Black - Brightwood" name="JosephBlack" gender="Male" VO_Status="Needs Recording" rel_version="Quest_MSQ2_WeaversFen">Ah, {playerName}! Look at that - The one axe of legend reforged anew\n\nYou'll decapitate many a damned soul yet. I hope to witness your glory.</string>
	<string key="9201_Cleric_00_Dialogue" speaker="Kristjan Magnuson - Weaver's Fen" name="KristjanMagnuson" gender="Male" VO_Status="Needs Recording" rel_version="Quest_MSQ2_WeaversFen">The bones I wear are all testaments to that life. Though their owners may have passed, they each taught me lessons of the healing arts.\n\nIf you wish to aid the suffering of those you meet, you must listen to the sounds beneath their skin.</string>
	<string key="9201_Cleric_01_Dialogue" comment="after provide to hope manifest" speaker="Kristjan Magnuson - Weaver's Fen" name="KristjanMagnuson" gender="Male" VO_Status="Needs Recording" rel_version="Quest_MSQ2_WeaversFen">You're a healer of sorts, I've met many blessed by your gifts. Eternal life means emotions unending, but with heroes like yourself, that cycle does not need to include suffering. \n\nI wonder if you might like a fitting emblem - a Staff of Life - a very potent one?</string>
	<string key="9201_Cleric_02_Dialogue" comment="after hope manifest" speaker="Kristjan Magnuson - Weaver's Fen" name="KristjanMagnuson" gender="Male" VO_Status="Needs Recording" rel_version="Quest_MSQ2_WeaversFen">With that staff in hand, you are the very thing, young one.\n\nHope Manifest, indeed.</string>
	<string key="9206_00_Guardian_Dialogue" speaker="Gwendolin Drake - Brightwood" name="GwendolinDrake" gender="Female" VO_Status="Needs Recording" rel_version="Quest_MSQ2_WeaversFen">Covenant, Syndicate, Marauders. They're all the same. Unprepared men with oversized egos.\n\nIf you wish to survive, let alone propser on Aeternum, you need fine armor, real armor. Not the matching leotards those fools wear.</string>
	<string key="9206_01_Guardian_Dialogue" comment="after new threat" speaker="Gwendolin Drake - Brightwood" name="GwendolinDrake" gender="Female" VO_Status="Needs Recording" rel_version="Quest_MSQ2_WeaversFen">This island is chaos incarnate. Between the waring factions and all the supernatural horrors, it seems every step is a battle lying in wait.\n\n There's no way around it, but through. We must learn to embrace the war within. No one said it would be easy, did they?</string>
	<string key="9206_02_Guardian_Dialogue" comment="after armor quest" speaker="Gwendolin Drake - Brightwood" name="GwendolinDrake" gender="Female" VO_Status="Needs Recording" rel_version="Quest_MSQ2_WeaversFen">Impressive! You are truly girded for war!\n\nBattle's Embrace will protect you from the worst of what the Corrupted or the Lost can throw at you.</string>
</resources>

