<resources xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<string key="99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove_morgaine_01_TalkTo_next2_prompt">"What type of enemies?"</string>
	<string key="99E_Sun_Edengrove_IGC" comment="TEMP" speaker="Sun Fuchun">Behold, Edengrove, the jewel of Aeternum! Here is a land where nature still commands. It’s thorny, poisonous, and beautiful, and you’ll never find in all the world such an abundance of peculiar flora.\nSpeaking of peculiar, did you know the life cycle of the Angry Earth begins in Edengrove? I’ve been studying them for ages, but always from a distance. It seems now we must study them ever more closely.\nThere is an enclave founded by the elder druids to the north; we will have to visit there... they undoubtedly hoard some of the knowledge we seek...</string>
	<string key="99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues_morgaine_armillary_greet" comment="TEMP" speaker="Morgaine">Go on then, deposit the crystals, activate Myrddin's infernal machine!</string>
	<string key="99E_MSQ_02_Morgaine_bark" comment="TEMP" speaker="Morgaine">That… that was Myrddin! Quickly, let us follow his instruction!</string>
	<string key="99E_MSQ_02_Myrddin_VO_Clue1" comment="TEMP" speaker="Myrddin">When time and space are suspended… words from past to future hold the key.</string>
	<string key="99E_MSQ_02_Myrddin_VO_Clue2" comment="TEMP" speaker="Myrddin">Words are but vessels. Prisons of meaning, where an idea, or a mind can be trapped.</string>
	<string key="99E_MSQ_02_Myrddin_VO_Clue3" comment="TEMP" speaker="Myrddin">Like the facets of these crystals, mind, heart and soul are just aspects of a singular thing. Take heed, sister.</string>
	<string key="99E_Adiana_Edengrove_Shrine_1" comment="TEMP" speaker="Adiana Theron">The forests of Edengrove are not places, they are entities in and of themselves, each speaking for its own, but with a shared voice.\nHere, the lives of our walking brethren begin in the Garden, but like us, we draw our strength from a deeper well.\nAll the children are fed by the mother, their sustenance drawn from the river flowing from the one true source.\nIf a limb becomes it infected, it must be severed to protect the source.</string>
	<string key="99E_Adiana_Edengrove_Shrine_2" comment="TEMP" speaker="Adiana Theron">Alone but alive, sustenance is needed, but never satiated.\nA thirst acquired like a contagion from our enemies, but of the Earth, and now within.\nThe needs felt are beyond those fitting for life; there is a desire to... spread.\nCome closer, others, feel the warmth of our evolved form, a new entity, immune to the enemy, but forever alone... cut off from the well.</string>
	<string key="99E_Adiana_Edengrove_Shrine_3" comment="TEMP" speaker="Adiana Theron">A melody emerges from the sounds of the natural world, a song of celebration.. and of lamentation.\nThe brilliance of new life blooming in the grove, and the dirge sung in memory of those whose sacrifice gave us our purpose.\nRivers within rivers provide the light of our vengeance, our fury, our power.\nThe childen of the Angry Earth are charges of the Motherwell, the source of our enemies' doom.</string>
	<string key="99E_MSQ_05_Myrddin_VO_Clue1" comment="TEMP" speaker="Myrddin">Well done, my liege! I hope your shield has protected you as well it has allowed for my protection in this instance. I will see you soon.</string>
	<string key="99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison_morgaine_06_TalkTo_next_2_prompt" comment="TEMP" speaker="UI - Player Prompt">"The key is close to the heart of those Myrddin loved…"</string>
	<string key="99E_MSQ_05_Myrddin_VO_Clue2" comment="TEMP" speaker="Myrddin">Well sister, now you know why I stole your pendant. Let us hope that was in cause of seeing us soon reunited.</string>
	<string key="99e_MSQ_06_Myrddin_Argument_IGC_1" comment="TEMP" speaker="Myrddin">Where am I? Is this real? Morgaine… is that you?</string>
	<string key="99e_MSQ_06_Myrddin_Argument_IGC_2" comment="TEMP" speaker="Morgaine">Brother!</string>
	<string key="99e_MSQ_06_Myrddin_Argument_IGC_3" comment="TEMP" speaker="Ser Galahad">Myrddin! At last!</string>
	<string key="99e_MSQ_06_Myrddin_Argument_IGC_4" comment="TEMP" speaker="Morgaine">It is me, though I am older, yet you've grown younger instead? And free of the Crimson Sorcerer?</string>
	<string key="99e_MSQ_06_Myrddin_Argument_IGC_5" comment="TEMP" speaker="Ser Galahad">Enough sibling sentimentality! Dammit Myrddin, where is Artorius? What have you done with him?</string>
	<string key="99e_MSQ_06_Myrddin_Argument_IGC_6" comment="TEMP" speaker="Myrddin">I…</string>
	<string key="99e_MSQ_06_Myrddin_Argument_IGC_7" comment="TEMP" speaker="Morgaine">Ignore the knight, brother. What is this place? How did you… I have so many questions!</string>
	<string key="99e_MSQ_06_Myrddin_Argument_IGC_8" comment="TEMP" speaker="Ser Galahad">And the FIRST is what happened to Artorius! Answer, wizard! Or I shall make you answer for the knights who fell by your hand!</string>
	<string key="99e_MSQ_06_Myrddin_Argument_IGC_9" comment="TEMP" speaker="Myrddin">I…</string>
	<string key="99e_MSQ_06_Myrddin_Argument_IGC_10" comment="TEMP" speaker="Morgaine">You tin-plated fool! Can't you put aside your obsession for even a moment?</string>
	<string key="99e_MSQ_06_Myrddin_Argument_IGC_11" comment="TEMP" speaker="Ser Galahad">The fate of our king? You! How dare you, witch!</string>
	<string key="99e_MSQ_06_Myrddin_Argument_IGC_12" comment="TEMP" speaker="Myrddin">Cease this foolish bickering, both of you!</string>
	<string key="99e_MSQ_06_Myrddin_Argument_IGC_13" comment="TEMP" speaker="Myrddin">Galahad… it's complicated. Within this prison, time and space blur. I see glimpses of the king. At times, he may even be real.</string>
	<string key="99e_MSQ_06_Myrddin_Argument_IGC_14" comment="TEMP" speaker="Ser Galahad">The king is… within?</string>
	<string key="99e_MSQ_06_Myrddin_Argument_IGC_15" comment="TEMP" speaker="Morgaine">The king's fate is long past, what matters now is the present.</string>
	<string key="99e_MSQ_06_Myrddin_Argument_IGC_16" comment="TEMP" speaker="Myrddin">Indeed, in truth, the most important message I have is for you, Soulwarden.</string>
	<string key="99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_myrddin_01_TalkTo_next2_prompt" comment="TEMP" speaker="UI - Player Prompt">"Even if we prevent that, how do we defeat her?"</string>
	<string key="99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_myrddin_01_TalkTo_next2" comment="TEMP" speaker="Myrddin" dialogue-next="@99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_myrddin_01_TalkTo_next3" dialogue-prompt="@99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_myrddin_01_TalkTo_next2_prompt">There are too many possibilities. I'm sorry to tell you, most of them do not end well, but listen to my sister. She's wiser than me anyhow.\n\nThe only thing I can tell you with confidence is to get that staff, and quickly.</string>
	<string key="99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_myrddin_01_TalkTo_next3_prompt" comment="TEMP" speaker="UI - Player Prompt">"Then what do we do with it?"</string>
	<string key="99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_myrddin_01_TalkTo_next3" comment="TEMP" speaker="Myrddin" dialogue-next="@99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_myrddin_01_TalkTo_next4" dialogue-prompt="@99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_myrddin_01_TalkTo_next3_prompt">The staff is a mighty artifact, beyond any other I ever made… and I made many. \n\nYou could cleanse it of Corruption, but that would take a source of immense power. I don't know. I… cannot remain here any longer.</string>
	<string key="99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_myrddin_01_TalkTo_next4_prompt" comment="TEMP" speaker="UI - Player Prompt">"Why do you have to leave?"</string>
	<string key="99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_myrddin_01_TalkTo_next4" comment="TEMP" speaker="Myrddin" dialogue-prompt="@99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_myrddin_01_TalkTo_next4_prompt">I have a temporal reprieve, one for which I sacrificed much. I may not get another.\n\nI must go. I sense Galahad wishes to follow. A foolish gesture, but I cannot stop him. Good luck, Soulwarden. I hope we meet again somehow.</string>
	<string key="99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_morgaine_08_TalkTo_next_2_prompt">"What about the Staff of Wizardry?"</string>
	<string key="99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_complete_available_response_next_2_prompt" comment="TEMP" speaker="UI - Player Prompt">"The Tempest seeks the Staff of Wizardry."</string>
	<string key="99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission_proposal_next3_prompt">"I can speak to her."</string>
</resources>

