<resources xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_SIMPLETASKCONTAINER_tooltip">Tasks can be completed in any order, but all must be complete to complete the container</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_CONSECUTIVETASKCONTAINER_tooltip">Tasks progress can only be completed in order</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_PARTIALTASKCONTAINER_tooltip">Container used for Quests that will complete when any of the containing tasks are completed. Any remaining tasks are disabled unless explicitly marked as Stay Active</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKKILL_tooltip">Get the &lt;b&gt;Killing Blow&lt;/b&gt; X times on an AI (optionally with a specific weapon)</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKKILLWITHWEAPONCLASS_tooltip">Get the &lt;b&gt;Killing Blow&lt;/b&gt; X times on an AI with a specific weapon class</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKCONTROLPOINT_tooltip">Task that tracks the state of a faction's territory possession</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_PATROLTASK_tooltip">Variant of TaskGoTo that completes once the player is in the location of a given duration. Requires AT LEAST one POITag or Territory ID, or both.</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKHAVELEVEL_tooltip">Succeeds if player is/achieves target level. If ItemName is provided for target Categorical Progression Id, then target level within that progression succeeds.</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKBUYSELL_tooltip">Mostly Deprecated, does  not work with Trading Post</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKCRAFTING_tooltip">DO NOT USE</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKTRIGGERAREA_tooltip">Triggers when the player is within a specific location</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKGOTO_tooltip">DO NOT USE</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKGOTOTERRITORY_tooltip">Variant of TaskGoTo that sends a player to a territory</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKGOTOPOITAG_tooltip">Variant of TaskGoTo that sends a player to a poi</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKGOTOPOITAGONTERRITORY_tooltip">Variant of TaskGoTo that sends a player to a poi on a specific territory</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKRECIPEPINNED_tooltip">Triggers when recipes are pinned, a specific one, or any if not specified</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKCRAFTRECIPE_tooltip">Recipe crafting, can be used for crafting stations</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKREFINERECIPE_tooltip">Refining Recipe (crafting, but with added check for recipe data flag \"IsRefining = true\"), can be used for crafting stations.</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKCRAFTWEAPONFAMILY_tooltip">Craft a weapon of the specified family (bow, sword, etc)</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKCRAFTITEMFAMILY_tooltip">Craft an Item of the specified family (e.g. Dye, etc.)</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKREFINEITEMFAMILY_tooltip">Refine craft an Item of the specified family (e.g. RefinedResource, etc.)</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKINVENTORY_tooltip">DO NOT USE</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKUSEITEMS_tooltip">The player needs to use the specific item</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKEQUIPITEM_tooltip">Item must be equipped onto the characters paperdoll</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKEQUIPWEAPONWITHWEAPONFAMILY_tooltip">Equip a weapon of the specified family with an optional gear score</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKGAMEEVENT_tooltip">A generic task that is triggered by a game event occurring</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKTRIGGERGAMEEVENT_tooltip">A task that triggers a game-event when active. Follows the same fields as TaskGameEvent</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKACHIEVEMENT_tooltip">Task that progresses when an achievement is completed, starts completed if player has already unlocked the achievement</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKTEMPORARYUNLOCKACHIEVEMENT_tooltip">Task that unlocks an achievement when task is added, and locks it when the task is removed (progress begins completed, nothing progresses this task). If you abandon or reset the quest for this task, it will lock the achievement.</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKUNLOCKACHIEVEMENT_tooltip">Task the unlocks an achievement when the task is added (progress begins completed, nothing progresses this task). If you abandon or reset the quest for this task after it has been activated, it will lock the achievement (set ShouldCheckPoints to true to suppress this functionality).</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKTEMPORARYLOCKACHIEVEMENT_tooltip">Task that locks an achievement when task is added, and unlocks it when the task is removed (progress begins completed, nothing progresses this task). If you abandon or reset the quest for this task, it will unlock the achievement.</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKLOCKACHIEVEMENT_tooltip">Task the locks an achievement when the task is added (progress begins completed, nothing progresses this task). By default, if you abandon or reset the quest for this task after it has been activated, it will unlock the achievement (set ShouldCheckPoints to true to suppress this functionality).</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKREADLOREINTERRITORY_tooltip">DO NOT USE</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKCHOOSEFACTION_tooltip">Task that completes when the player has completed faction selection.</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKCONVERSATIONSTATE_tooltip">Task that completes when the player enters a particular conversation state</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKCONVERSATIONTOPIC_tooltip">Task that completes when the player chooses a particular conversation topic.  Will not be completed until the player has fully progressed through all dialogues in the conversation topic, and has exited the conversation.</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKOBJECTIVE_tooltip">Task that adds an additional objective to the player, and tracks it through until completion.</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKKILLCONTRIBUTION_tooltip">Occurs if the player &lt;b&gt;contributes to a kill&lt;/b&gt; or destroy (optionally with a specific weapon class)</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKHAVEITEMS_tooltip">Looks at the owner's inventory for the given items. Using &lt;i&gt;ChestDropProbability&lt;/i&gt; (for chest drops) and &lt;i&gt;ItemDropVC / ItemDropProbability&lt;/i&gt; (for kills) on the same TaskHaveItem provides the objective item from both kills and chests.</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKHAVEANDRETURNITEMS_tooltip">Is removed upon completion</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKGATHERITEMS_tooltip">Must be collected by gathering</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKGATHERANDRETURNITEMS_tooltip">Must be collected by gathering and is removed upon completion</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKHAVEITEMSWITHWEAPONFAMILY_tooltip">Look at the player's inventory for a weapon of the specified family and optionally a gear score</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKHAVEITEMSWITHITEMFAMILY_tooltip">Look at the player's inventory for an item of the specified family and optionally a gear score</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKGIVEITEM_tooltip">Gives the player an item and may remove it.</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKGIVEANDTAKEITEM_tooltip">Is removed upon completion</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKREMOVEITEM_tooltip">Removes the specified item amount from the inventory and paperdoll slots (it won't check global storage yet).</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKSALVAGEITEM_tooltip">Occurs when the player salvages the given item</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKSPECIFICINTERACT_tooltip">Untested. Same properties as TaskInteract, but can grey out the interact text when this task isn't active. Tracks unique entities with a matching Interact tag the player has interacted with.</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKINTERACT_tooltip">Interact with an object (succeeds upon interact completion)</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKJOINGUILD_tooltip">Task completes if player joins a company</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKDIE_tooltip">Task is completed if player dies</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKOPENUISCREEN_tooltip">Occurs when the player opens the specific UI screen</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKTIMER_tooltip">Task is completed if specified time expires</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKFISHINGEQUIP_tooltip">Task is completed when the player equips a fishing pole.</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKFISHINGCAST_tooltip">Task that tracks the number of times the player has cast their fishing line</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKFISHINGHOOK_tooltip">Task that tracks the number of times the player has hooked a fish</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKFISHINGREEL_tooltip">Task that tracks the number of times the player has reeled in a catch successfully (fish or non-fish)</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKFISHINGHOTSPOTANY_tooltip">Task that tracks the number of successful catches from any hotspot</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKFISHINGHOTSPOTCATEGORY_tooltip">Task that tracks the number of successful catches from a specified category of hotspot</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKFISHINGCATCHANYFISH_tooltip">Task that tracks the number of times the player has reeled in a fish successfully (like TaskFishingReel but wont increment on catching a boot or seaweed)</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKFISHINGCATCHFISH_tooltip">Task that tracks the number of times the player has caught a particular fish (small bass, medium bass, large salmon, etc)</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKFISHINGCATCHWEIGHT_tooltip">Task that tracks the number of time the player has caught a fish &gt; a specified weight</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKFISHINGCATCHLENGTH_tooltip">Task that tracks the number of time the player has caught a fish &gt; a specified length</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKFISHINGCATCHRARITY_tooltip">Task that tracks the number of times the player has caught a fish &gt; a specified rarity</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKREQUIREGATHERITEMS_tooltip">This task only increments progress when the player actually gathers something, not just when they already have the items in their inventory. Does not work with quest items.</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKGATHERCYCLICSTATE_tooltip">This task increments progress when the player gathers the specified cyclic gatherable state. Set StayActive to true to make it so progress will regress after the task is completed if the player gathers the wrong state.</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKHOUSESCORE_tooltip">Have at least one house with the specified decoration score</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKGAMEMODE_tooltip">Task that progresses when the player enters the target Game Mode. Each game mode has a unique ID, these can be found in &lt;i&gt;JavelinData_GameModes.xml&lt;/i&gt;</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKCLAIMBUTTON_tooltip">Task that completes when it receives the OnClaimButtonPressed message and the objective IDs match.</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKPERIODICCHALLENGEDAILY_tooltip">Task that tracks the number of times daily challenges have been completed.</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKPERIODICCHALLENGEWEEKLY_tooltip">Task that tracks the number of times weekly challenges have been completed.</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKCOMPLETEOBJECTIVETYPE_tooltip">Task that tracks the number of objectives of a certain type.</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKCOMPLETEDUNGEON_tooltip">Progresses when the player completes the final phase of ANY dungeon game mode</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKPERFORMSONG_tooltip">Progresses when the player completes a performance of the target song</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKPERFORMEMOTE_tooltip">Progresses when the player performs an emote for the emote's gatherable duration</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKQUICKCOURSE_tooltip">Task for timed or untimed quests that require the player to follow a sequential list of checkpoints. E.g. mount race</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKSLAYERSCRIPT_tooltip">Task that triggers a block of slayerscript- use caution when applying this task!</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKEXITPOITAG_tooltip">Variant of TaskGoTo that sends a player outside a POI</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKEXITTERRITORY_tooltip">Variant of TaskGoTo that sends a player outside of a territory</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKEXITPOITAGONTERRITORY_tooltip">Variant of TaskGoTo that sends a player outside of a POI and outside of a territory</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKCUTSCENECOMPLETE_tooltip">Task for detecting the ending of a specific cutscene</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKCINEMATICSTART_tooltip">Task for detecting the starting of a specific cinematic video</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKCINEMATICCOMPLETE_tooltip">Task for detecting the ending of a specific cinematic video</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_NONE_tooltip">NONE</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKREPAIRITEM_tooltip">DO NOT USE</string>
	<string key="ObjectiveTaskType_TASKBUILDSTRUCTURE_tooltip">DO NOT USE</string>
	<string key="BackupDirectoryKey_0">QuestToolV2/BackupRecoveryData</string>
	<string key="BackupLocalizationDirectoryKey_0">Localization</string>
	<string key="BackupLocalizationHistoryKey_0">LocalizationHistory.xml</string>
	<string key="BackupLocalizationHelperKey_0">LocalizationHelper.txt</string>
	<string key="BackupLocalizationSafeDirectoryKey_0">UnrecoveredLocalization</string>
</resources>

